I can't believe Goblins got
this far past our defenses!
I know, and there seems
to be no end to them!
I think there might be too
many for us to deal with!
I bet they're here cause
Renvichi abandoned his post!
He probably did, that coward.
You won't be afraid, you won't be afraid.
You won't be afraid, you won't be afraid!
I'm a fresh feeling, and I'm a faith.
I'm a false expectation,
and I'm a righteous person.
Maybe it's so good,
but I'm a true thought.
I'm not without you, but I'm ready.
For the easy to say, I'm
just interacting with you.
I'm sure you're nothing wrong
with the wrong behavior.
I'm just asking you,
it's only a right moment.
Oh?
I must return to my station. Now.
But then, if I went back,
I'd just be in the way.
Renly.
Poor child.
It seems that you are broken.
broken I
have no choice
but to punish you with deep
freeze despite the
double-winged blades choosing
you as their master you've
never achieved perfect
weapon control over them
as a knight Good night,
you are lacking something most crucial.
Good night, Renly.
Did you hear that?
Her eminence made you good night!
What a lucky boy you are!
I'm so jealous!
I am a failure.
A fail...
It does not matter whether I exist or not.
What about here?
Sure, this tent looks
like it'll be safe enough.
We'll tuck him away in back and
stand guard at the entrance.
It's so dark.
Is someone there?
It is I.
I did not mean to startle you.
Oh, Sir Knight!
Forgive our intrusion. No.
I am at fault here.
And please, be at ease.
I am no longer a knight.
I am a deserter.
The unit I was assigned to
command must be in a panic by now.
I am sure some have died.
And yet, I hide here in
safety, like a filthy coward.
Where are my manners?
We haven't introduced ourselves yet.
My name is Ronie Arabelle.
This is Tiese Streenin.
And the one behind her...
That's Elite Disciple Kirito.
Kirito?
He is the one who killed the Pontifex?
Sir Knight, forgive me
if I'm being impertinent,
but since you're here,
could you please help us?
We hate to ask, but you see, we gave our
word we'd keep Kirito safe no matter what.
We're still primary trainees.
We can't defend ourselves
against things like goblins yet.
Even so, we accepted this responsibility.
We have to keep him safe.
Lady Alice is counting on us, too.
Oh no!
The enemy's already here!
I see smoke!
What?
Are they setting the tents on fire?
There's no fire.
Just a whole lot of this
weird-looking smoke.
Wait.
Now I can see shapes moving around in it.
A goblin?
Hookie here!
I found me some white-heeled girlies!
What a lucky day!
He's sick!
I'm going to win the
tournament today, Renly.
No, I am.
Huh?
Too slow!
R-Ren, please.
Stay back!
I'm warning you!
So feisty, so tasty!
If you come any closer, I'll kill you!
Are you...
are you trying to protect these two?
You struggle to Even though you cannot
stand Or speak Or draw your sword While I
cower.
Ren Li.
I want you to become a great knight.
Do it for me.
Sir Knight!
You did it!
You saved us!
Thank you so much!
Stay here, please.
And protect Kirito.
Y-yes, sir!
I am Renly, Integrity
Knight, Renly Synthesis 27.
If you want my head, then be
ready to give your lives for it!
Chop him to pieces!
I can do this.
By now, the smoke should be
clearing from the front lines.
All I have to do is hold out a
little longer and help will arrive.
Are you their commander?
Yeah, i be kosugi, chief
of the mountain goblins.
What a shame!
You done killed some of my best warriors.
Surprised to find ye here?
You being an integrity knight and all.
Why ain't you be where the
action is with the other knights?
That is none of your concern. Now perish!
Thought I was just another
goblin, did you, boy?
Well, I ain't so impressed
with you either, to be honest.
You said before you were
an Integrity Knight.
I was told one of you
could take on a thousand.
But that ain't the case
for you now, is it?
That's why you be hiding
all the way back here.
Ain't that right?
It seems that you are broken, child.
Perhaps she was right.
I am a failure.
Maybe I am.
You are correct I am not
much of a knight even so let
us be clear Though I might
be defective these are not
Double wings.
Take flight!
I can do this all day, boy!
Release.
Recollection!
Beautiful.
Quit playing around!
Ren-li-ji?
Well, well, well.
Someone's gotten a bit more knightly.
We were hoping to get
credit for saving you.
Too bad you had to spoil that.
No one's gonna care that we chopped
off way more heads than you did.
Sir Knight, we humbly request your orders.
Very well, then.
Keep Kirito and the girls safe.
You don't have to worry about that.
We handed them all off to
the supply core just now.
We should secure the area, then.
We killed all the goblins here.
If that is the case, then I suppose
we'd best return to our units. Yes, sir.
As you command.
Thank you.
Lord Sigur Osig, Lord Shibori, and
Lord Kosogi have all been killed.
Useless wretches!
Demihumans can't be
counted on for anything.
Have you located all the
Integrity Knights yet?
Currently, we have the three on
the front lines in our sights.
We found two more among their rear units,
but we do not have a fix on them yet.
There are only five knights here?
Impossible, unless that
is all they ever had.
Regardless of how many there are
here, we must slaughter them all.
Go on, wake the minions.
Have them fly for 700 mils, then
descend upon the battlefield.
And kill everything.
Forgive the question, but won't our
demi-human units get caught in that? Too bad.
Right.
How many minions do you wish?
We have 800 available.
They are all hatched and ready to go.
Send every last one of them.
Here they come
I'm splitting sword...
Air slice!
Uncle activated his
perfect weapon control.
He has made his move.
You imbecile how did we not know they
had such a large unit of mages they don't
i i don't know what
happened have they
deployed their flying dragons yet no? No.
The skies above the battlefield are clear.
Not one dragon has been spotted.
Then there can be only
one explanation for it.
That must be perfect weapon control.
They're knight's special skill.
Damn them.
They're stronger than I thought.
Using a weapon that way is risky, though.
It would drain massive
amounts of the knight's life.
How could they unleash such a barrage?
I just got word, m 'lady.
Our spotter's located the
two knights in the rear.
We've targeted them.
We now have all five
of them in our sights.
Good.
I have waited for this.
It is my chance for glory,
and I shall seize it.
Ogre archers and dark mages, advance
into the ravine Once you are in position,
ready the bows And begin
the incineration incantation
Mage unit prepare for wide-range
incineration projectiles
Spotters begin the
incantation to guide the
projectiles to the
integrity Knights position
Ogres prepare to fire
Why is it that the souls of the fallen
below, whether human or demi-human,
generate sacred power
that is so warm and pure?
The people of the human empire and the
monsters of the dark territory have,
essentially, the same souls.
The only difference is
whether they were born
on one side of the End
Mountains or the other.
If so, then why are they...
why are we fighting?
Kirito, if you were here...
No.
I raised my sword against the
Pontifex and defied the Axiom Church.
It is my duty to see this through now.
They're here.
As far as maintaining elements,
I am no match for what thousands
of dark mages are capable of.
And converting sacred power into
fire or ice elements would not be a
potent enough art to sap all the spatial
resources rising from the ravine.
However, sealing luminous elements inside
a mirror would reflect them infinitely.
System call!
Generate thermal element!
It's not working what's
going on what do we do we
can't activate the projectiles
without thermal elements!
Damn why isn't the incantation
working archmage if i
may i think all the spatial
resources have been depleted!
What are you insane that's impossible
what about all the screaming scores of
both humans and demi-humans have died
already if those resources aren't here?
then where do they all go?
The burden of taking countless lives for
the sake of one shall be mine to bear.
Bloom! Flowers!
First element.
Let's go.
Oh